Guide to the Leah Salisbury Papers
Rare Book and Manuscript Library Columbia University Libraries
- Series III: Arranged Correspondence and Manuscripts
  - Salaway, Lowell (Box 270)
  - Salloway (Box 270)
  - Salvatore, George (Box 270)
  - Samson, Anne (Box 270)
  - Scenic Designers (Box 271)
  - Schach, Leonard (Box 271)
  - Sachankman, Benjamin M. (Box 271)
  - Schmidt, Annie M.G. (Box 271)
  - Schmidt, Harry A. (Box 271)
  - Schoenfeld, bernard C. (Box 271)
  - Schramm, Wilbur (Box 271)
  - Schwartz, Herbert A. (Box 271)
  - Schwerin, Doris Halpern; Jules Victor Schwerin & Rhoda Bellak (Box 271)
  - Seaton, George (Box 272)
  - Seff, Linda (Box 272)
  - Seff, Manuel D. (Box 272)
  - Selby, Dennis (Box 272)
  - Selden, George (Box 273 & 274)
  - Sergel, Christopher (Box 275)
  - Sergel, Kristin (Box 275)
  - Sergel, Roger L. (Box 275)
  - Sergel, Sherman Louis (Box 275)
  - Seton, Cynthia (Box 275)
  - Settel, Arthur (Box 275)
  - Shaber, David (Box 275)
  - Shane, Margaret (Box 275)
  - Shapiro, Louis (Box 275)
  - Shapiro, Sidney (Box 275)
  - Sharmat, Stephen William (Box 275)
  - Shatnoff, Judith (Box 275)
  - Shavelson, Melville (Box 275)
  - Shaw, Arthur (Box 275)
  - Sheekman, Arthur (Box 275)
  - Sheldon, Edward Brewster (Box 275)
  - Shelton, Edgar G., Jr. (Box 275)
  - Shelton, Robert E. (Box 275)
  - Shepherd, Jean (Box 275)
  - Sherie, Fenn & Ingram D'Abbes (Box 275)
  - Sherman, Harold M. (Box 275)
  - Sherwood, Robert Emmet (Box 275)
  - Shevin, Fred & Elaine (Box 275)
  - Shewmaker, Eugene F. (Box 275)
  - Shonbrun, Margaret Thomson (Box 275)
  - Short, Robin (Box 275)
  - Siebenhandel, Frank (Box 276)
  - Siegel, Max (Box 276)
  - Silver, Arnold (Box 276)
  - Silver, Lee (Box 276)
  - Silver, Warren A. (Box 276)
  - Silverstein, Irving (Box 276)
  - Simcoe, Ben (Box 276)
  - Simich, Michael J. (Box 276)
  - Simon, Peggy (Box 276)
  - Skutch, Robert (Box 276)
  - Slater, Max (Box 276)
  - Slattety, Martin & William D'Toole (Box 276)
  - Sloane, Sidney (Box 276)
  - Small, William J. (Box 276)
  - Smith, Dodie (Box 276)
  - Smith, George Alan (Box 276)
  - Smith, Joe Bates (Box 276)
  - Smith, Richard (Box 276)
  - Smith, Rayall (Box 276)
  - Smith, Stanley E. (Box 276)
  - Smith, Warren Sylvester (Box 276)
  - Smolin, Jay H. (Box 276)
  - Smythe, Norman Lawrence (Box 276)
  - Snider, Richard H. (Box 276)
  - Snow, V. Douglas (Box 276)
  - Snyder, William (Box 277)
  - Sobel, Stanford (Box 278)
  - Society of Authors' Representatives (Box 280 278)
  - Soffer, Sam (Box 280 278)
  - Solomon, Louis et al. (Box 279)
  - Somerfeld, Robert (Box 280)
  - Sorell, Walter (Box 280)
  - Sorensen, E. Per (Box 280)
  - Soulat, Robert (Box 280)
  - Southgate, Howard (Box 280)
  - Spanier, Ginette (Box 280)
  - Spencer, Franz (Box 280)
  - Spencer, Ray E. (Box 280)
  - Spewack, Sam & Bella (Box 280)
  - Spitzer, Marian (Box 281)
  - Stanton, V.K. (Box 281)
  - Starling, Lynn (Box 282)
  - Starr, Ben (Box 283)
  - Stauffér, Don (Box 283)
  - Stavis, Barrie (Box 283)
  - Stefanini, Prima (Box 283)
  - Steigman, B.M. (Box 283)
  - Stein, Sol (Box 283)
  - Steinthardt, Herschel S. (Box 283)
  - Stern, Harold (Box 283)
  - Stern, Richard G. (Box 283)
  - Stetson, Helen Sloan (Box 283)
  - Stettner, Louis (Box 283)
  - Stevens, Clifford & Joseph Asher (Box 283)
  - Stevens, Robert E. (Box 283)
  - Stewart, James (Box 283)
  - Stigdon, Clem & Pat (Box 283)
  - Stigler, W.A. (Box 283)
  - Stock, Irvin (Box 283)
  - Stone, Leroy (Box 283)
  - Storey, David Malcolm (Box 283)
  - Storm, Leslie Correspondence: Black Chiffon (Box 284)
  - Storm, Leslie Mss. Black Chiffon (Box 235)
  - Storm, Leslie Mss. -- Royalty Statements (Box 286)
  - "Story Information" (Box 287)
  - Streger, Paul (Box 287)
  - Strong, Michael (Box 287)
  - Strum, J. Maury (Box 287)
  - Stubbs, Kenneth [Kenn Stuart] (Box 287)
  - Sturn, Justin (Box 287)
  - Styler, Adele (Box 287)
  - Sugarman, Robert (Box 287)
  - Summer & Winter Stock Theaters (Box 287)
  - Sutherland, Dan (Box 287)
  - Sweeney, Thomas & Richard Boyd (Box 287)
  - Sykes, Gerald (Box 287)
  - Sze, Mai-Mai (Box 287)
  - Szogyi, Alex (Box 287)
  - Taradash, Daniel (Box 288)
  - Tarcher, Jeremy P. (Box 288)
  - Tarpley, Trista (Box 288)
  - Tarr, Herbert (Box 288)
  - Taylor, Marian (Box 288)
  - Teasdale. Russell E. (Box 288)
  - Teitelbaum, Maurice J. (Box 288)
  - Television - Networks, Agencies, etc. (Box 288)
  - Temple, Joan (Box 289)
  - Terry, Paul (Box 289)
  - Thacher, Russell (Box 289)
  - Thatcher, Edwin (Box 289)
  - Thom, Robert (Box 289)
  - Thomas, A.E. (Box 289)
  - Thomas, Bob (Box 289)
  - Thomas, G.A. (Box 289)
  - Thomas, Lee (Box 289)
  - Thomas, Rachel (Box 289)
  - Thompson, Eric (Box 289)
  - Thompson, Harlan (Box 289)
  - Thompson, Harlan Manuscripts (Box 290)
  - Thomsen, Robert (Box 291)
  - Thorne, Garry (Box 291)
  - Thorne, Jerome K. (Box 291)
  - Tillerna,C.H. (Box 291)
  - Tobey, Kenneth (Box 291)
  - Todd, Jane S. (Box 291)
  - Toohey, John Latham (Box 291)
  - Topping, C. Wesley (Box 291)
  - Tothers, Don (Box 291)
  - Tourea, M.B. (Box 291)
  - Townsend, Leo (Box 291)
  - Towsen, A.N. (Box 291)
  - Treadwell, Sophie (Box 292)
  - Treece, Henry (Box 292)
  - Tresidder, Argus John (Box 292)
  - Trilling, Diana Rubin (Mrs. Lionel) (Box 292)
  - Truly, Henry (Box 292)
  - Tryon, Tom (Box 292)
  - Tugend, Harry (Box 293)
  - Tuning, William (Box 294)
  - Tunney, Kieran (Box 294)
  - Tuttle, Florence W. (Box 294)
  - Tyler, Converse (Box 294)
  - Tyler, Evelyn (Box 294)
  - Tyrrell, Brad (Box 294)
  - Tyszka, Walter (Box 294)
  - Ullman, Gloria (Box 294)
  - Untermeyer, Louis (Box 294)
  - Usshar, Bruno David (Box 294)
  - Vale, Eugene (Box 294)
  - Valentino, Rudolph Photographs (Box 294)
  - Valla, Mary (Box 294)
  - Vane, Norman Thaddeus (Box 294)
  - Vein, Norman T. (Box 294)
  - Ventura, Charles (Box 294)
  - Vogel, Joseph (Box 294)
  - vonHoffman, Nicholas (Box 294)
  - Vornholt, John (Box 294)
  - Vuilleumier, John F. (Box 294)
  - Vuolo, Louis (Box 294)
  - Waagenaar, Sam (Box 295)
  - Waggner, George (Box 295)
  - Wakefield, Gilbert (Box 295)
  - Walden, William (Box 295)
  - Waldorf, Wilella (Box 295)
  - Waldron, Eli (Box 295)
  - Walker, Gerald (Box 295)
  - Wall, Bud (Box 295)
  - Walpole, Helen (Box 295)
  - Walsh, Norman (Box 295)
  - Ward, Alec S. (Box 295)
  - Ward, Mary Jane (Box 295)
  - Ward, St. John (Box 295)
  - Waren, Helen (Box 295)
  - Warner, Eugene (Box 295)
  - Warrington, J. Stuart (Box 295)
  - Warshawsky, Samuel J. (Box 295)
  - Watson, Donald (Box 296)
  - Watt, Douglas (Box 297)
  - Webster, Margaret (Box 297)
  - Weil, Dorothy (Box 297)
  - Weill, Kurt (Box 297)
  - Weiser, Jacob A. (Box 297)
  - Weiss, Allan (Box 297)
  - Weiss, Neil (Box 297)
  - Weitzenkorn, Louis (Box 297)
  - West, Nathaniel (Box 297)
  - Wendell, Winifred Lee (Box 297)
  - Welsh, Sheperd (Box 297)
  - Wexler, Charles S. (Box 297)
  - Wexler, Norman (Box 297)
  - Wexler, John (Box 297)
  - Whedon, John (Box 298)
  - Wheel, Patricia (Box 298)
  - Wheeler, Joan (Box 298)
  - White, Dana (Box 298)
  - Whitelaw, Arthur (Box 298)
  - Whitney, Arthur O. (Box 298)
  - Whittington, Hugh Gorman (Box 298)
  - Wickey, Lawrence & Paul Goldman (Box 298)
  - Wilde, Hagar (Box 298)
  - Wilder, Alec (Box 298)
  - Wilder, Thornton (Box 298)
  - Williams, George Llyonel (Box 298)
  - Willman, Noel (Box 298)
  - Wilson, Mitchell (Box 298)
  - Winslow, Thyra Samter (Box 298)
  - Winston, Irene (Box 298)
  - Wise, David (Box 298)
  - Wiseman, Philip (Box 298)
  - Witcover, Walt (Box 298)
  - Witwer, Andrew (Box 298)
  - Wolfe, Glenn (Box 298)
  - Wolquitt, Eleanor (Box 298)
  - Wong, Anna May (Box 298)
  - Worms, Jeannine (Box 298)
  - Wormser, Judy (Box 298)
  - Wray, Fay (Box 298)
  - Wright, Edward T. (Box 298)
  - Writers Newsletter (Box 298)
  - Wyden, Peter (Box 298)
  - Wyeth, Henrietta (Box 298)
  - Yalman, Tune (Box 298)
  - Yates, Peter (Box 298)
  - Yordan, Philip (Box 299)
  - Young, Howard Irving (Box 300)
  - Young, Stark Correspondence (Box 301)
  - Young, Stark Manuscripts Reviews, etc. Royalty Statements (Box 302)
  - Zavin, Ben & Carl Leo (Box 303)
  - Zinn, Howard (Box 303)
  - Zuckerman, Albert J. (Box 303)
  - Misc. (Box 303)
- Series IV: Financial Records
  - Financial Records: --Bills and Accounts (Box 304)
  - Financial Records: --Cancelled Checks, 1962 (Box 305)
  - Financial Records: --Check Registers, 1942 (Box 306 & 307)
- Series V: Readers' Reports
  - Readers' Reports 1942-l960: Arranged by Author, A -K (Box 308)
  - Readers Reports, 1948-1960: Arranged by Author, L-Z (Box 309)
  - Readers' Reports: Arranged by Title, A-B (Box 310)
  - Readers' Reoorts: Arranged by Title, C & D (Box 311)
  - Readers' Reoorts: Arranged by Title, E - G (Box 312)
  - Readers' Reports: Arranged by Title, H - K (Box 313)
  - Readers' Reports: Arranged by Title, L - M (Box 314)
  - Readers' Reports: Arranged by Title, N - P (Box 315)
  - Readers' Reports: Arranged by Title, Q - R (Box 316)
  - Readers' Reports: Arranged by Title, S (Box 317)
  - Readers' Reports: Arranged by Title, T - U (Box 318)
  - Readers' Reports: Arranged by Title, V - Z (Box 319)
- Series VI: Printed Material
  - Printed --Books, Periodicals, and Programs (Box 320)
  - Printed --Books inscribed to Leah Salisbury (Box 321)
- Series VII: Card Files
  - Card files with information pertaining to scripts. Filed A-Z by title. Also headings such as "Author rewriting," "Pictures," Foreign," "Stock," etc. (Box 322)
  - Card file of authors and their scripts, A-Z (Box 323)
  - Card file of scripts by title, A-I (Box 324)
  - Card file of names and places, A-Z and stories, A-Y (Box 325)
  - Card file of authors of plays returned, A-Z and movie talent, A-W (Box 326)
  - Card file of plays returned to authors, A-Z by title (Box 327)
- Series VIII: Reviews and Publicity
  - Playbills, programs, reviews, clippings, publicity, etc. for various productions (Box 345)